# SERGEI KHLOPOFF

#### SUMMARY

Bringing over 17 years experience in the broadcast, film and video industries. Providing web development, creative, design and marketing services to a broad range of online, corporate, private, entertainment and start-up clients. Successfully evolving with new technologies while maintaining excellent communication and problem solving skills in both one-on-one and team environments.

#### MOMENTS OF NOTE

- 2002 Axiem Silver Award Finalist: Interactive Category "Fresher Software: Matisse CD"
- 2001 Telly Award "AmericaOne: Race for the America's Cup 2000"

## QUALIFICATIONS

- Joomla
- WordPress
- Dreamweaver
- HTML / XHTML / CSS
- Adobe Creative Suite

- CMS
- Database Management
- Content Development and Editing
- Social Media / Community Relations
- Avid Media Composer

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### [ 2012 ]

Star Media Group / The Maytum Company

#### Web Development Manager

- Implement new database and CMS solutions for company's online products and services.
- Develop websites for marketing agency departments.
- Update social media presence.
- Consult and coordinate online solutions for agency clients.
- Supervise Content Managers.
- Create training materials on CMS systems.

[ 2010 – 2012 ]

DigEdition

## Content Manager

- Edit and publish news and marketing submissions for online community portal.
- Test, report and consult on company's CMS software products.
- Apply Facebook, Twitter, YouTube, Flickr and email to engage community relations.
- Produce tutorial training videos.

[ 2002 – Current ]

Smackalicious

# Owner, Creative Director, Designer

- Consultant, Web Developer, Web Designer, Flash UI Designer, Motion Graphic Designer, Avid Video Editor and DVD Author for education, entertainment, ecommerce, fashion design, healthcare and software start-up companies.
- Art direction, motion graphic design, and supportive video editing on independent film.
- Director, Producer, Videographer and Editor on independent music documentaries.

[ 1998 – 2002 ]

Foxxdance Productions

## Creative Director

- Artistic direction and quality control of corporate, commercial and entertainment media.
- Consulting, pre-production, directing, producing, scriptwriting, storyboarding, videography, editing and graphic/motion design of broadcast quality video.
- Author, design packaging and output final content for web streaming and new media duplication.

BFA, Printmaking with Animation Pacific Northwest College of Art, Portland, OR

Individual Contract Based Major in conjunction with film and animation studies at the Northwest Film Center.

Ongoing Continuing Education courses focusing on web development, Adobe Creative Suite, Avid Media Composer, Final Cut Pro, After Effects, Flash Actionscript, 3D modeling and animation and introduction to Linux: Unix.